I'm Peppa Pig.
[OINKS]
This is my little brother
George.
This is mummy Pig.
And this is daddy Pig.
[OINKS]
[LAUGHTER]
Peppa Pig. Oink.
[PEPPA READING
ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Today is Mummy Pig's birthday.
Daddy Pig has made Mummy Pig
breakfast in bed.
Happy birthday Mummy Pig!
Oink!
Peppa and George have made
Mummy Pig a birthday card.
Happy Birthday Mummy!
Oink! Oink!
Oh! What a lovely
birthday surprise!
And there are more
surprises to come!
Enjoy your
birthday breakfast!
Take your time.
[GIGGLING]
Mmm! Yummy!
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
Quick! We have to get
everything else ready!
Daddy Pig has made
a birthday cake for Mummy Pig.
Oink! We've just got
to put the candles on!
[GIGGLING]
One.. Two...
Here I come!
Mummy Pig has finished
her birthday breakfast.
Mummy's coming!
Oh no!
We're not ready yet!
[KNOCKING]
Uh, who is it?
It's Mummy.
Can I come in?
No! No! Oink!
Is there something
secret going on?
Er, no, nothing's going on.
Oink!
But you can't come in.
Oink! I see.
[GIGGLE]
Mummy Pig. Why don't you
relax in the sitting room?
That's sounds nice.
Well, it is your birthday!
Oink! Okay, Peppa.
I think I know where
the sitting room is!
[LAUGHS]
Oink! Here's a nice magazine.
Thank you, Peppa.
And here's some pretty music.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING
OVER RADIO]
Thank you, Peppa.
[GIGGLES]
[GIGGLING]
Oink! We need the same number
of candles as Mummy's age.
One... two... three...
Oh dear.
We haven't got
nearly enough candles.
Daddy? How old is Mummy?
I'll whisper it in your ear.
[WHISPERING]
Wow! Really old!
[LAUGHS]
Oink! You know, I think
three candles will be fine.
Mummy Pig's
birthday cake is ready!
Hurrah
[LAUGHTER]
We just have to put up
the decorations
in the sitting room.
[YAWNS]
Hello Mummy!
Ah, there you all are!
I was getting a little bored.
Mummy? Would you like to have
a nice walk in the garden?
[LAUGHS]
Oink! Do I have any choice?
Nope!
[LAUGHS]
Bye, bye Mummy!
Have a lovely walk! Oink!
We'll call you when it's safe
to come back in.
I'd forgotten what hard work
birthdays were!
[LAUGHS]
[LAUGHING]
Daddy Pig, Peppa and George are
decorating the sitting room.
[LAUGHS]
[CAR HONKS]
Granny and Grandpa Pig
have arrived
for Mummy Pig's birthday.
Oink!
Happy Birthday Mummy Pig!
Aren't you coming inside?
Oh, I can't come in yet.
Daddy Pig, Peppa and George
are doing secret things
for my birthday.
How lovely! Oink!
See you later!
Bye!
[LAUGHS]
Mummy, would you like
to come inside now?
I'd love to.
Close your eyes!
Keep your eyes closed Mummy!
[LAUGHS]
DADDY:
One... two... three...
Open your eyes!
[PARTY HORNS]
Happy Birthday Mummy Pig!
[LAUGHING AND OINKING]
Blow the candles out... Oink!
And make a wish!
[LAUGHS]
Mummy, Mummy!
Open your present!
Oink! I've no idea!
Open it and see.
It's a beautiful dress!
[GASPS]
You're beautiful, Mummy.
Oink, oink!
Now you just need
somewhere nice to wear it.
What's this?
Two tickets
to the theatre!
Tonight! Oink!
Thank you! Oink!
Mummy Pig loves going
to the theatre.
And Granny Pig and I are going
to babysit the little ones.
Hurrah!
What a super birthday!
I'm the luckiest Mummy
in the whole world! Oink!
And the most beautiful!
[LAUGHTER]
[PEPPA READING
ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George are having
their favourite food:
spaghetti!
[OINKS,
THEN LAUGHS]
What a lot of noise!
Oink! Finished!
Oink! Oink!
Ah, now we'll have
a bit of quiet!
[LAUGHS]
Oink! What's that?
It's a tooth!
Where did that come from?
[LAUGHS]
Peppa, maybe you should
look in the mirror!
Oink!
[LAUGHING]
Oh!
[LAUGHTER]
It's my tooth! Oink!
It's fallen out!
MUMMY:
Don't worry Peppa.
It's just a milk tooth.
They're meant to fall out.
Will I grow a new one, Mummy?
MUMMY:
Yes you will Peppa.
It also means the Tooth Fairy
will be paying you a visit.
Tooth Fairy?
Yes, the Tooth Fairy.
If you put the tooth under
your pillow tonight,
the Tooth Fairy will come.
Oink! Oink!
The Tooth Fairy
will take the tooth.
And in it's place,
she will leave a shiny coin!
Oink! Oink!
Oink! When I grow up,
I want to be a Tooth Fairy!
[LAUGHS]
Oink! And what would you like
to be when you grow up, George?
Dine-Saw!
[LAUGHS]
A dinosaur!
[LAUGHTER]
Quick George,
it's bedtime!
Oink! We don't want
to miss the Tooth Fairy!
Before going to bed, Peppa and
George brush their teeth.
Peppa, what are you doing?
Oink! I'm brushing my tooth
so it's nice and clean
for the Tooth Fairy.
[LAUGHTER]
Peppa cannot wait
to get into bed.
Peppa is putting her tooth
under the pillow
for the Tooth Fairy.
Goodnight Peppa and George.
Oink!
[LAUGHS,
THEN OINKS]
[LAUGHS]
Goodnight Mummy!
Oink! Goodnight Daddy!
Oink!
Goodnight my little piggies!
[DOOR CLOSES]
[LAUGHS]
George,
I'm not going to sleep! Oink!
Lets both stay awake all night
and see the Tooth Fairy!
Oink!
[LAUGHTER]
This Tooth Fairy is very late!
[SIGHS]
The Tooth Fairy is taking
a long time to arrive.
Where is that Tooth Fairy?
[SNORING]
What is that noise?
Is it the Tooth Fairy?
George, can you hear something?
[SNORING]
Oh, George!
Oh, the noise is George.
He was so tired,
he has fallen asleep.
George is not very good
at staying awake but I am.
I've got to stay awake
and see the Tooth Fairy.
I'm not going to sleep.
[SNORING]
The Tooth Fairy has arrived.
Oink! Oink!
But Peppa is asleep.
[MUMMY PIG'S VOICE]
Hello Peppa.
Would you like this coin
in return for your tooth?
[SNORES]
What a nice clean tooth.
Thank you, Peppa.
Goodnight.
Peppa, George, wake up.
It's morning.
What?
I wasn't asleep!
Did the Tooth Fairy come?
No.
Let's take a look
under your pillow.
Look, Peppa!
The Tooth Fairy has been
and she's left you a coin!
Hooray!
[LAUGHS]
You fell asleep, didn't you?
Well, maybe I fell asleep
just for a little bit. Oink!
Next time I will stay awake
and I will see the Tooth Fairy!
[LAUGHTER]
[PEPPA READING
ONSCREEN TEXT]
[LAUGHTER]
NARRATOR:
Today, Peppa and her family
are going for a drive
in their red car.
Oink! Shall we have
the roof down?
Yes, please!
Oink! Oink!
[LAUGHTER]
Peppa and George
love their car.
Is everybody ready?
Ready!
Then let's go!
[CAR HONKS]
Oink! I love our car!
[LAUGHS]
And our car loves us too!
Don't you?
[CAR HONKS]
[LAUGHTER]
[ENGINE MAKING STRANGE NOISES]
Oh dear, the car does
not sound very well.
Oink! What's wrong Daddy?
Hm!
Uh, I don't know.
Oink! Let's take it
to Granddad Dog's Garage.
He can fix it.
That's a good idea,
Mummy Pig. Oink!
Woof!
Granddad Dog
runs the garage.
He is very good
at mending cars.
[CAR HONKS]
Woof!
Oh dear, Daddy Pig!
Your car does not
sound very well.
[CAR MAKES STRANGE NOISE]
Can you fix it please,
Granddad Dog?
Yes...
but it will take all day.
Oh...
Oink! We wanted to go
for a drive in our car.
Woof!
Don't worry.
You can borrow this new car
while I fix yours.
Hurrah!
[LAUGHTER]
Thank you, Granddad Dog.
Would you like the roof down?
Oink! Yes, please!
I'll just press
this red button.
What a clever car!
[GASPING]
Woof! When you come back
I will have fixed your car.
Thank you,
Grandad Dog.
Oink! Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye.
Oink! Oink!
Goodbye!
Peppa and her family
like the new blue car.
There are so many buttons
in this new car.
PEPPA:
Oink! What does
the green button do, Daddy?
Let's see.
Magic windows!
[LAUGHTER]
Daddy! Make the magic windows
go down.
[LAUGHTER]
Oink! What does
the blue button do?
I don't know.
Let's see.
[LOUD ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Ah!
[LAUGHTER]
Oink! I love this new car.
Can we keep it?
No, we can't keep it, Peppa.
We've only borrowed
it for today.
[BOTH GROAN]
[DISTANT THUNDER]
Oh no, I think
it's going to rain.
Yes, I'll just put
the roof up. Oink!
Now, which is the button
to close the roof?
[CAR HONKS]
[LAUGHTER]
Oops! Silly Me.
Ah ha, this must
be the button.
Argh!
The new car has squirted
Daddy Pig with water.
[LAUGHTER]
Silly Daddy,
that's not the roof!
This button!
Oops! Not that one.
[LOUD ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[CAR ALARM SOUNDING]
Help!
Daddy Pig has forgotten
which button closes the roof.
I don't think this car likes me!
Let's try the red button.
[ALARM STOPS]
Hurray!
[LAUGHTER]
But now
it's stopped raining.
Oink! Can we
open the roof again?
Er, yes.
Which button was it?
The red one!
Hurray!
[LAUGHTER]
[CAR HORN HONKS]
Granddad Dog has fixed the car.
Your car is fixed. Woof!
Hurray!
Thank you Granddad Dog,
and keep the change.
Thank you,
Daddy Pig.
Woof! Woof! Goodbye!
Oink! Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye.
Oink! Oink!
Ah! It's good to get
our old car back again! Oink!
I liked the new car,
but I like our old car better.
And I think our old car
likes us too.
Don't you?
[CAR HONKS]
[LAUGHTER]
[PEPPA READING
ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Granny and Grandpa Pig
are making
a treasure hunt
for Peppa and George.
Granny Pig is drawing
the treasure map.
Grandpa Pig
is burying the treasure
in a secret place
in the garden.
Grandpa Pig!
Have you finished?!
Peppa and George
will be here soon!
[LAUGHS]
Oink! No need to panic,
Granny Pig!
Peppa and her family are here!
Quick Grandpa Pig!
They're here!
Almost done!
[LAUGHTER]
[SIGHS]
Grandpa Pig
just finished in time!
Granny Pig! Oink!
We're here!
Grunt! Ganggy Ig!
Oink!
Hello my little ones!
Grandpa Pig!
Baba Ig!
Ahoy there,
me hearties!
Peppa, George, we've made
you a treasure hunt!
Oink! Somewhere in the garden
is buried treasure!
Wow! Treasure!
Oink! Where is it?
You have to look for it.
Here's a treasure map
for Peppa.
And George can
wear my pirate hat.
Ahoy there,
Captain George!
[OINKS,
THEN LAUGHS]
Oink!
The map is a bit difficult.
Daddy can you help?
Of course Peppa.
I'm very good with maps.
Er. It is a bit difficult.
Daddy Pig, you're holding
the map upside down!
Yes, I thought as much. Oink!
PEPPA:
It's easy!
The red cross shows
where the treasure is!
DADDY:
But where in the garden
are those two apple trees?
Hmm, I don't know.
Would you like a clue?
Yes please!
Oink!
The first clue
is in a bottle.
Oink!
But where is the bottle?
Oink! I can see it!
[LAUGHTER]
Peppa has found
the first clue.
A message in a bottle.
Oink! Look everyone!
Here's the bottle!
Oink! Oink!
Well done, Peppa! Oink!
Let's see what
the message says.
Oh, it's a message
from a pirate!
Mummy? Can you read
the pirate's message?
Hmm. This pirate
has very bad handwriting...
The pirate's handwriting
is excellent.
No, I can't
make it out at all.
The pirate has clearly written,
“Follow the arrows!”
Follow the arrows?
Oink! Oink!
George has found
the second clue!
Sticks in the shape
of an arrow!
Look! They point this way!
[LAUGHING]
Peppa and George
are following the arrows.
PEPPA:
Look George! A key!
Peppa has found the next clue.
A key!
Well done, Peppa!
Oink!
Now you just have to find
the treasure chest
that it unlocks.
But there aren't
any more clues.
Maybe you should take another
look at the map...
Look Peppa, the map
has two apple trees on it.
Here's an apple tree! Oink!
And here's an apple tree!
Oink! Oink!
So the treasure must be here!
Let's take a look!
[GRUNTING]
Oh dear. There doesn't seem to
be anything here...
[HOLLOW THUDS]
Hang on!
There is something here!
Wow! Treasure!
ALL:
Hurray!
[LAUGHTER]
Well done,
well done.
[LAUGHTER]
I've got the key to open it!
Wow! I can't believe it!
Gold coins!
They must be worth a fortune!
It's better than that!
They are not gold coins,
they are chocolate coins!
And there's a chocolate coin
for everybody.
ALL:
Hurray!
[LAUGHTER]
Peppa and George
love chocolate coins.
Everyone loves
chocolate coins.
Granny, Grandpa.
This is the best
treasure hunt ever!
[LAUGHTER]
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLING]
PEPPA:
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING, GIGGLING]
[GRUNTING]